The camera...
Good for you, Ron.
He's so cute.
Why?
Hi, Ron.
Can you change that, please?
This is Ron.
Cute little Ron.
And you, Lenka.
I'm Renka Iwamoto.
I'm Rhythm.
I'm 13 years old.
I'm fat.
Okay, Teresa.
I'm Teresa Ikeda.
This is Maru-chan.
I guess I've grown, or maybe I'm just starting to change since I came in.
Number seven.
This is Rocco. He's 2 years old.
We haven't had a dog here for a while.
It's only been a few minutes since we've seen each other.
The dog team brought him here.
He's very energetic. - He's the most energetic one here.
He's the most energetic dog I've ever seen.
He's cute.
He's mad.
Rocco, let's be friends today.
You've been driving me crazy all day.
Nice to meet you, Rocco.
He's so cute!
I'm having fun.
Wow.
It's fun.
Hi, Lee.
Lee-chan!
Meow!
I'm going to turn my back on you.
Oh, Ron!
Ron might be in the way
Mai-chan!
Liz, sit?
Liz, can you sit down?
Liz.
Liz, do you read me?
Uncle Liz, do you read me?
Uncle Liz?
Uncle Liz, can you sit down?
Uncle Liz, I need you to stop.
Uncle Liz! Uncle Liz!
Grandpa.
Grandpa, you look different.
Liz.
I used to be able to do a lot of things.
Liz shows off her skills
The end.
Liz's special skill is that she doesn't listen to other people.
She's so cute. She goes at her own pace.
Liz.
She's so fast-paced.
Rocco, what can you do?
Rocco, can you do something?
You just did.
Rocco!
Sit down.
Rocco, sit.
Why don't you sit down?
Sweet.
You're sweet on dogs.
Rocco!
Rocco, sit.
Sit.
One moment
Paw.
Aah! Aah!
ah!
Welcome back.
Sit.
You eat.
All right, I'll give it to you.
That's sweet.
Rourke, high five?
High five?
You're so cute! Cute!
Rourke, did you get a hug?
That's intense.
Rourke, can I get a hug?
Hug, hug, hug, hug.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
You've always been able to do that, haven't you?
Liz, sit.
Sit.
Sit, right?
Oh, Rico!
Yes!
Rico!
I'll do 50.
Ron! Come here!
Ron-kun, Rocco!
Ron-kun, Roco-chan!
Hey, Ron, this is Rocco.
Mr. Ron.
Liz! Liz!
Liz, this is Rocco.
Liz. Liz.
Liz.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Liz, you're not interested in other dogs, are you?
Hey, Ron.
Liz, talk to me.
Rocco!
He attacked my butt.
Coco is fine.
Coco! Coco!
Coco, Coco, Coco.
Coco, Coco, Coco!
Nebita is being pushed around.
Fatty Liz!
You're not fat!
I'm not fat.
You're the sweaty type.
Liz, you're the sweaty type.
Hi, Liz.
He's wagging his tail so much.
He's so cute.
Liz, let me see.
Here it is.
So cute!
When I went with Ms. Manatsu Kamakura...
I had him dig it up for me.
I just drank it.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
It suits you.
Oh!
Congratulations.
Oh.
LOL
Oh!
Coco.
Here we go.
Okay.
Ah!
Hey, Coco.
Don't leave it there.
Just a little bit more.
Can you bring it to me?
Come on, Coco.
Ah!
Coco!
Laughing.
Coco, that's good luck!
Coco, that's...
No, no, no.
Coco.
Coco-chan
Coco, Coco, Coco, Coco, Coco, Coco, Coco, Coco
Over here.
Won
LOL!
def
ana
I'm not sure.
Heyla 다음에茶路いいike 14 loss
Mari Because I prefer long rolls
uh
I don't think so.
You can go first.
Yay.
I got it.
Give me this.
Oh, my God, give me the ball.
Come here. Come here.
I love it. I love it.
Give me some balls.
I like it. I like it.
I like it.
Let go of the ball.
Throw me the ball.
Mr. Frog, me or Ron?
Which one of us are you going to take care of?
I don't know.
Mr. Ron?
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
For today
I went to get a trim.
I know.
About a week ago.
She's so cute!
He's so cute!
It looks delicious.
I want some water.
It's okay, Liz.
Forget the camera.
Just focus on the water.
It's okay, Liz.
It's almost over, Liz.
Oh, my God, you're so cute.
Liz got a cuddle.
That's great.
Liz, look over there.
Look over there.
Oh, he's so cute.
Cute doggie.
It's like there's two doggies.
He's so cute.
Good for you.
Good for you, Ron.
That's great.
So fluffy.
I love a pretty girl, don't you?
Liz, you stink.
It doesn't stink.
In your eyes.
I'd like to take a couple of shots.
Hey, Toco.
Let's get a couple of shots, Toco.
Oh, I got it!
Two shots of Toko!
Shall we take a cute picture together?
Let's do it.
It's a keepsake.
Look at the angle of this shot.
Everybody's in the shot, everybody's in the shot.
Everybody's in the picture.
Wait, wait, wait.
Misachu, look at Misachu.
Oh, my God!
It's good, it's good!
She's looking at the camera!
It's perfect!
Come here, come here, come here.
Oh, that's good! How do you like it?
Here you go!
Go, go, go!
You think you can do it? Hey, Lobo.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Get it, Lobo!
Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
One more time!
I can't see Nao.
Ah! Here it comes!
Thank you!
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Oh, his face is so cool.
You're not mad.
I'm not mad.
Rourke, stand by.
He's crying so hard.
Rourke's talking... his eyes are breaking my legs.
He's stomping his feet so hard.
Dad. - Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Help!
Vartan's curious, too.
He smelled Liz.
And then he turned around.
Dinner's here.
Rourke, dinner's here.
Rourke, dinner's ready!
Rourke, not yet.
Rourke, sit down.
Wait, wait, wait.
He's kind of sitting down.
Liz, where are you sitting?
She's trying to eat.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
He just ate it.
Liz, is it good?
Sit down.
It's delicious.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Another one.
Come on, baby.
I can't wait for you to eat.
High five.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm ready.
You're early, Liz.
Liz, you're early.
Liz.
You're eating too much food, aren't you?
It's gone, Liz.
It's gone.
Oh, no, no, no.
You can eat.
I'm done.
Liz, you jumped in.
Is it good, Marutan?
Look, Liz, there's still some left.
Do you like it, Marutan?
Rourke, you don't want some?
Liz, I'm going to eat it all.
Liz, look, it's going up.
It's going up.
Oh, Ron, they're eating you.
Ron, they're eating you.
Ron, you left the broccoli so beautifully.
Look, he ate it.
Was it good? Oh, it's on your mouth.
You've got broccoli on your mouth.
Oh, Rocco, you're so good.
Eat it.
We all ate it.
Rocco, you're so good!
Rocco and Liz are in the training section.
Marutan flavor!
Thanks for the food.
Next year
we had a great time, didn't we?
We all had a lot of freedom.
We had a lot of free time.
It was the first time for me to meet your dogs.
I've never seen them before.
It was a very fulfilling day.
It was a great day!
See you soon!
If possible, we'll do the second one.
again!
I'd like to invite a lot of people.
I hope we can do it again.
So, please subscribe to our channel
Subscribe to our channel
High rating
Good Button
High rating and Good button are the same thing, right?
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye!
Woof! Woof!
Woof! Woof! Woof!
Woof. Woof. Woof.
I'm real.